Guide to the Robert Flaherty Film Seminar Archive 1949 - 2011 MSS.326
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Flaherty Film Seminars, 253680
  - Subseries A: Audio Recordings, 253681
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, June 8, 1999; ID: 326.0620; 257510 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0620)
      Remarks by Mark McFaddin, Scott Stark, Tom Whiteside (Moderator), Rob Koegler (Recording), Jason (Recording)
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, June 9, 1999; ID: 326.0621; 257511 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0621)
      Original Number: 1999-13
      Morning Session, Intro remarks: Orlando Bagwell, Jackie Jones, Discussion: Same as above, Recording: Jack
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, June 9, 1999; ID: 326.0622; 257512 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0622)
      Original Number: 1999-14
      Afternoon Session, Phillip Mallory Jones, Catherine Milton
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, June 8, 1999; ID: 326.0623; 257513 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0623)
      Original Number: 1999-15
      Afternoon Session, Intro Remarks: R. Herskowtiz, Jennifer and Kevin McCoy
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, June 9, 1999; ID: 326.0624; 257514 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0624)
      Original Number: 1999-16
      Evening Session: Intro: R. Herskowitz, Caspar Straacke, Discussion: Laura Marks (Moderator), Caspar Straacke (Discussion)
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, June 10, 1999; ID: 326.0625; 257516 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0625)
      Original Number: 1999-17
      Morning Session: Intro: Orlando Bagwell, Discussion: John Else, Johann van der Keuken, Final Evaluation Session
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, 2000; ID: 326.0626; 257517 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0626)
      Original Number: 2000-01
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, June 17, 2000; ID: 326.0627; 257518 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0627)
      Original Number: 2000-02
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, June 17, 2000; ID: 326.0628; 257519 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0628)
      Original Number: 2000-03
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, June 17, 2000; ID: 326.0629; 257520 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0629)
      Original Number: 2000-04
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, June 18, 2000; ID: 326.0630; 257521 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0630)
      Original Number: 2000-05
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, June 18, 2000; ID: 326.0631; 257522 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0631)
      Original Number: 2000-06
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, June 19, 2000; ID: 326.0632; 257523 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0632)
      Original Number: 2000-07
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, June 19, 2000; ID: 326.0633; 257531 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0633)
      Original Number: 2000-08
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, June 19, 2000; ID: 326.0634; 257532 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0634)
      Original Number: 2000-09
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, June 20, 2000; ID: 326.0635; 257534 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0635)
      Original Number: 2000-10
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, June 20, 2000; ID: 326.0636; 257545 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0636)
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, June 21, 2000; ID: 326.0638; 257546 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0638)
      Party
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, June 21, 2000; ID: 326.0637; 257549 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0637)
      Unknown contents.
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, June 22, 2000; ID: 326.0639; 257551 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0639)
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, June 22, 2000; ID: 326.0640; 257553 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0640)
      Coz
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, June 15, 2001; ID: 326.0641; 257556 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0641)
      Original Number: 2001-01
      Films: Trut, Herman Slobbe, Beauty Will Change the World (excerpt),
      Guests: Heddy Honigmann, Carl Svenstedt
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, June 16, 2001; ID: 326.0642; 257557 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0642)
      Original Number: 2001-02
      Jo Anne Birnie Danzker, Photo slide show of Flaherty
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, June 16, 2001; ID: 326.0643; 257560 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0643)
      Original Number: 2001-03
      Robert Flaherty Photographs/Slide Show,
      Guest: Jo Anne Birnie Danzker
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, June 16, 2001; ID: 326.0644; 257561 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0644)
      Original Format: HHB DAT
      Original Number: 2001-04
      Saadia: Women of the Moroccan Resistance
      Guest: Tania Cypriano
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, June 16, 2001; ID: 326.0645; 257562 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0645)
      Original Number: 2001-05
      Ex Voto Odo Ya! Guest: Tania Cypriano
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, June 16, 2001; ID: 326.0646; 257563 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0646)
      Original Number: 2001-06
      Crazy Guest: Heddy Honigmann
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, 2001; ID: 326.0647; 257564 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0647)
      Original Number: 2001-07
      Obon, Origin, Heartbeat
      Guest: Andrej Zdravic
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, June 18, 2001; ID: 326.0648; 257565 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0648)
      Original Number: 2001-08
      Brave New Land, Guest: Lucia Murat
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, 2001; ID: 326.0649; 257566 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0649)
      Original Number: 2001-09
      The Underground Orchestra, Guest: Heddy Honigmann
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, 2001; ID: 326.0650; 257568 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0650)
      Original Number: 2001-10
      My Grandmother's Camera, Guest: Tania Cypriano
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, 2001; ID: 326.0651; 257569 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0651)
      Original Number: 2001-11
      Metal and Melancholy, Guest: Heddy Henigmann
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, 2001; ID: 326.0652; 257571 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0652)
      Original Number: 2001-12
      Fast Runner, Guest: Norm Cohen
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, 2001; ID: 326.0653; 257572 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0653)
      Original Number: 2001-13
      Seers and Clowns, Africa, Witch Madness, Our Spirited Earth, W.O.W.
      Way to Father's Village
      Faith Hubley, Richard Funy
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, 2001; ID: 326.0654; 257573 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0654)
      Original Number: 2001-14
      Pigeon Within, One Self: Fish Girl, Blue Vinyl,
      Guests: Emily Hobley, Judith Helfand, Dan Gold
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, 2001; ID: 326.0655; 257574 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0655)
      Original Number: 2001-15
      Guests: Emily Hobley, Judith Helfrand, Dan Gold
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, 2001; ID: 326.0656; 257575 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0656)
      Original Number: 2001-16
      Delivery Man, Blake Ball, Excerpt from Hedwig & the Angry Itch and Death by Design
      Emily Hobley
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, 2001; ID: 326.0657; 257576 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0657)
      Original Number: 2001-17
      Breath Puddles [Phenix] Guest: Andrej Zdravic
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, 2001; ID: 326.0658; 257577 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0658)
      Original Number: 2001-18
      Dirty Laundry Sea in the Blood
      Richard Fong
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, 2001; ID: 326.0659; 257578 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0659)
      Original Number: 2001-19
      Independent Spirits, Her Grandmother's Gift, My Universe Inside Out,
      Guests: Sybil de Guardia, Patty Wineapple, Emily Hobley, Faith Hobley
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 20, 2001; ID: 326.0660; 257579 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0660)
      Original Number: 2001-20
      Threat
      Guests: Norm Cohen Carl Svenstedt
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 21, 2001; ID: 326.0661; 257580 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0661)
      Original Format: Quantegy DAT
      Original Number: 2001-21
      End of discussion with Carl & Norm
      Wrap up discussion
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 22, 2001; ID: 326.0662; 257582 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0662)
      Original Number: 2001-22
      Hubley Interview with Tarik
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, June 14, 2002; ID: 326.0663; 257583 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0663)
      Original Number: 2002-01
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, June 15, 2002; ID: 326.0664; 257584 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0664)
      Original Number: 2002-02
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, June 15, 2002; ID: 326.0665; 257586 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0665)
      Original Number: 2002-03
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Uman Discussion Tape, June 15, 2002; ID: 326.0666; 257587 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0666)
      Naomi Uman Discussion
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, June 15, 2002; ID: 326.0667; 257588 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0667)
      Original Number: 2002-04
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, June 16, 2002; ID: 326.0668; 257589 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0668)
      Original Number: 2002-05
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, June 16, 2002; ID: 326.0669; 257590 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0669)
      Original Number: 2002-06
      Title: A Burning Star, Guest: Kenji Onishi, Moderator: Ed Halter, Recordist: Juan Castito
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, June 16, 2002; ID: 326.0670; 257591 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0670)
      Original Number: 2002-07
      Title: A Burning Star Guest: Kenji Onishi Moderator: Ed Halter Recordist: Juan Casteto
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, June 16, 2002; ID: 326.0671; 257592 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0671)
      Original Number: 2002-08
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, June 17, 2002; ID: 326.0672; 257593 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0672)
      Original Number: 2002-09
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Anger Tape, June 17, 2002; ID: 326.0673; 257594 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0673)
      Kenneth Anger
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, 2002; ID: 326.0674; 257595 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0674)
      Original Number: 2002-10
      Fotopoulos/Oshina Shorts
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, June 18, 2002; ID: 326.0675; 257596 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0675)
      Original Number: 2002-11
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, June 18, 2002; ID: 326.0676; 257597 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0676)
      Original Number: 2002-12
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, June 19, 2002; ID: 326.0677; 257598 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0677)
      Original Number: 2002-13
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, June 19, 2002; ID: 326.0678; 257599 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0678)
      Original Number: 2002-14
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, 2002; ID: 326.0679; 257600 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0679)
      Original Number: 2002-15
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, 2002; ID: 326.0680; 257601 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0680)
      Original Number: 2002-16
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, June 20, 2002; ID: 326.0681; 257602 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0681)
      Original Number: 2002-17
      Hitler's Hat - Jeff Kruwk
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, June 20, 2002; ID: 326.0682; 257603 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0682)
      Original Number: 2002-18
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - June 21st A.M., June 21, 2002; ID: 326.0683; 257604 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0683)
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Unmarked, 2002; ID: 326.0684; 257605 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0684)
      Discussion following Hitler's Hat with J. Krulik Moderator: Ed
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, June 14, 2003; ID: 326.0685; 257606 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0685)
      Original Number: 2003-01
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, June 15, 2003; ID: 326.0686; 257607 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0686)
      Original Number: 2003-02
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, June 15, 2003; ID: 326.0687; 257608 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0687)
      Original Number: 2003-03
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, 2003; ID: 326.0688; 257609 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0688)
      Original Number: 2003-04
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, June 16, 2003; ID: 326.0689; 257610 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0689)
      Original Number: 2003-05
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, June 16, 2003; ID: 326.0690; 257611 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0690)
      Original Number: 2003-06
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, June 16, 2003; ID: 326.0691; 257612 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0691)
      Original Number: 2003-07
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, June 16, 2003; ID: 326.0692; 257613 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0692)
      Original Number: 2003-08
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, June 17, 2003; ID: 326.0693; 257614 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0693)
      Original Number: 2003-09
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, June 17, 2003; ID: 326.0694; 257615 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0694)
      Original Number: 2003-10
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, June 18, 2003; ID: 326.0695; 257616 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0695)
      Original Number: 2003-11
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, June 18, 2003; ID: 326.0696; 257617 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0696)
      Original Number: 2003-12
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, June 18, 2003; ID: 326.0697; 257618 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0697)
      Original Number: 2003-13
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, June 19, 2003; ID: 326.0698; 257619 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0698)
      Original Number: 2003-14
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, June 19, 2003; ID: 326.0699; 257621 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0699)
      Original Number: 2003-15
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, June 20, 2003; ID: 326.0700; 257622 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0700)
      Original Number: 2003-16
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, June 19, 2003; ID: 326.0701; 257623 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0701)
      Original Number: 2003-17
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, June 13, 2004; ID: 326.0702; 257624 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0702)
      Original Number: 001
      Jennifer Reeves, Robert Breer, Janie Geiser, Peter Hutton, Phil Solomon
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, June 13, 2004; ID: 326.0703; 257625 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0703)
      Original Number: 002
      What Mozart Saw - Burkhardt/Cornell
      Killer of Sheep - C. Burnett
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, June 13, 2004; ID: 326.0704; 257626 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0704)
      TRT: 00:05:00
      Original Number: 003
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, June 14, 2004; ID: 326.0705; 257627 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0705)
      TRT: 01:55:20
      Original Number: 005
      Moderator: William Sloan, Ricky Leacock, Michel Braulf
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8A, June 15, 2004; ID: 326.0706; 257628 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0706)
      Original Number: 008 A
      Pancho Villa, Director's Commentary and life [Buitar]
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8B, 2004; ID: 326.0707; 257629 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0707)
      Original Number: 008 B
      Guests: Gregario Raha, Andreas Guarim
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, June 15, 2004; ID: 326.0708; 257637 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0708)
      Original Number: 009
      10th Flaherty Seminar, Guest: Jennifer Reeves Programmer: Susan Oxtoby
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, June 16, 2004; ID: 326.0709; 257638 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0709)
      Original Number: 010
      Wednesday June 16, 2004 Afternoon Program by Ruth Brodey and Louis Massiah
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, June 17, 2004; ID: 326.0710; 257639 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0710)
      Original Number: 011
      10th Flaherty Seminar Guest: Morgan Fisher Lewis Klahr
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, June 16, 2004; ID: 326.0711; 257640 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0711)
      Original Number: 012
      Superbia; Journeys; Themes; Short Fuse
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, June 17, 2004; ID: 326.0712; 257641 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0712)
      Original Number: 013
      Media Activism and Public Access 50th Flaherty Seminar Guests: Dede Hallek George Stoney
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, June 17, 2004; ID: 326.0713; 257642 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0713)
      Original Number: 014
      The 50th Flaherty Programmer: Susan Octoby Artists: Peter Hutton and Ulrike Ottinger
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, June 18, 2004; ID: 326.0714; 257643 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0714)
      Original Number: 015
      The 50th Flaherty Seminar "The Cod World" by Shirley Clarke Moderator: Deedee Halleck
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, [undated]; ID: 326.0715; 257644 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0715)
      Original Number: 016
      The 50th Flaherty Seminar discussion session about "Southeast passage: A journey to the new blank spots on the map of Europe" (Part I) Guest: Ulrike Ottinger (Director)
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, [undated]; ID: 326.0716; 257645 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0716)
      Original Number: 017
      50th Flaherty Seminar George Stoney "getting out"
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, June 18, 2004; ID: 326.0717; 257646 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0717)
      Original Number: 018
      50th Flaherty Seminar Louise Bourque Morgan Fischer
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, [undated]; ID: 326.0718; 257647 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0718)
      Original Number: 019
      50th Flaherty Seminar Guest: Clive Holden Film: "Trains of Winnipeg" Programmer: Susan Oxtoby
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 01, June 11, 2005; ID: 326.0719; 257648 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0719)
      Original Format: Audiocassette
      Original Number: 2005-01
      Opening Comments
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 02, June 12, 2005; ID: 326.0720; 257649 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0720)
      Original Number: 2005-02
      Discussion 2-A
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 03, June 12, 2005; ID: 326.0721; 257650 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0721)
      Original Number: 2005-03
      Discussion 2-B
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 04, June 12, 2005; ID: 326.0722; 257651 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0722)
      Original Number: 2005-04
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 05, June 13, 2005; ID: 326.0723; 257652 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0723)
      Original Number: 2005-05
      Discussion 3-A
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 06, [undated]; ID: 326.0724; 257653 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0724)
      Original Number: 2005-06
      Leandro Katz slide show
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 07, [undated]; ID: 326.0725; 257654 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0725)
      Original Number: 2005-07
      Discussion 3-B
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 08, March 3, 2005; ID: 326.0726; 257655 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0726)
      Original Number: 2005-08
      6B Discussion 3B
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 09, June 13, 2005; ID: 326.0727; 257656 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0727)
      Original Number: 2005-09
      Discussion 3A
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, June 13, 2005; ID: 326.0728; 257657 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0728)
      Original Number: 2005-10
      7B Discussion 3-C
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, June 14, 2005; ID: 326.0729; 257658 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0729)
      Original Number: 2005-11
      Discussion 4-A
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, June 14, 2005; ID: 326.0730; 257659 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0730)
      Original Number: 2005-12
      Discussion 4-B
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, June 14, 2005; ID: 326.0731; 257660 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0731)
      Original Number: 2005-13
      Discussion 4-C
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, June 14, 2005; ID: 326.0732; 257661 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0732)
      Original Number: 2005-14
      Discussion 4-D
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, June 15, 2005; ID: 326.0733; 257662 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0733)
      Original Number: 2005-15
      Discussion 5-A
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, June 15, 2005; ID: 326.0734; 257663 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0734)
      Original Number: 2005-16
      Discussion 5-B
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, June 16, 2005; ID: 326.0735; 257664 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0735)
      Original Number: 2005-17
      Discussion 6-A
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, June 16, 2005; ID: 326.0736; 257665 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0736)
      Original Number: 2005-18
      Discussion 6-B
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, June 16, 2005; ID: 326.0737; 257666 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0737)
      Original Number: 2005-19
      Discussion 6-C
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 20, June 18, 2005; ID: 326.0738; 257667 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0738)
      Original Number: 2005-20
      Discussion 8-A
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 21, June 17, 2005; ID: 326.0739; 257668 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0739)
      Original Number: 2005-21
      Discussion 7-A
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 22, June 17, 2005; ID: 326.0740; 257669 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0740)
      Original Number: 2005-22
      Discussion 7-B
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 01, June 17, 2006; ID: 326.0741; 257670 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0741)
      Original Format: DAT
      Original Number: 2006-01
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 02, June 18, 2006; ID: 326.0742; 257671 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0742)
      Original Number: 2006-02
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 03, June 18, 2006; ID: 326.0743; 257672 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0743)
      Original Number: 2006-03
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 04, June 18, 2006; ID: 326. 0743; 257673 (Box 15, Media ID: 326. 0743)
      Original Number: 2006-04
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 05, June 18, 2006; ID: 326.0745; 257674 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0745)
      Original Number: 2006-05
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 06, June 19, 2006; ID: 326.0746; 257675 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0746)
      Original Number: 2006-06
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 07, June 19, 2006; ID: 326.0747; 257676 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0747)
      Original Number: 2006-07
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 08, June 19, 2006; ID: 326.0748; 257677 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0748)
      Original Number: 2006-08
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 09, June 19, 2006; ID: 326.0749; 257678 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0749)
      Original Number: 2006-09
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, June 20, 2006; ID: 326.0750; 257679 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0750)
      Original Number: 2006-10
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, June 20, 2006; ID: 326.0751; 257680 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0751)
      Original Number: 2006-11
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, June 20, 2006; ID: 326.0752; 257681 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0752)
      Original Number: 2006-12
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, 2006; ID: 326.0753; 257694 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0753)
      Original Number: 2006-13
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, 2006; ID: 326.0754; 257708 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0754)
      Original Number: 2006-14
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, June 21, 2006; ID: 326.0755; 257710 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0755)
      Original Number: 2006-15
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, June 22, 2006; ID: 326.0756; 257695 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0756)
      Original Number: 2006-16
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, June 22, 2006; ID: 326.0757; 257696 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0757)
      Original Number: 2006-17
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, 2006; ID: 326.0758; 257697 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0758)
      Original Number: 2006-18
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, June 22, 2006; ID: 326.0759; 257698 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0759)
      Original Number: 2006-19
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 20, June 22, 2006; ID: 326.0760; 257712 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0760)